filma24.org 2018-04-22

# Info - Filma24.org

### DMCA

Disclaimer: [Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) is not in anyway associated with filma24,tv, azfilma.al, filmaon.com, filma24hd.com, filmahd.al, filmaindian.com, albkino.co, deshtaku.com, filma4k.com, mosfli.tv, videotekaime.com, filma24.us, nukshtyhet.com, filma.co, filmaonline.net, filmakokoshka.com, filmiyt.net, ejashiko.com, mosrri.org, shihfilma.com, filma247.com, alfilma.com, titrashqip.al, skagjum.com, and other sites. We do not host any videos on[Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/). [Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) is absolutely legal and contains only links to other third party websites that translates movies like filma24,tv, azfilma.al, filmaon.com, filma24hd.com, filmahd.al, filmaindian.com, albkino.co, deshtaku.com, filma4k.com, mosfli.tv, videotekaime.com, filma24.us, nukshtyhet.com, filma.co, filmaonline.net, filmakokoshka.com, filmiyt.net, ejashiko.com, mosrri.org, shihfilma.com, filma247.com, alfilma.com, titrashqip.al, skagjum.com, and other sites. [Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) is not responsible for the compliance, copyright, legality, decency, or any other aspect of the content of other linked sites. If you have any legal issues please contact the appropriate media file owners or linked hosting websites. [Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) only and only provides links to third party sites links which are uploaded by third party users. [Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) is in no way affiliated with them!

### Privacy Policy

**Personal Information**  
[Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) is committed to protecting your privacy online.  
We are also committed to providing you with the very best experience we can on our web site. 

**IP address and logging**  
Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information and to track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc). 

**Credit card details**  
[Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) will never ask for Credit Card details and request that you do not enter it on any of the forms on [Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/). 

**External Sites.**  
[Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) is not responsible for the content of external internet sites.  
You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Cookies**  
Some ads displayed may come from our servers. Ads loading from our servers may also contain cookies, the purpose of these cookies is just to introduce and select the proper advertisements to be shown for your interests. We only have access to information of visiting frequencies of our visitors from cookies you might receive while viewing ads from our servers. A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows [Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) to recognize you each time you visit this site(customisation etc). Cookies themselves do not contain any personal information, and [Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) does not use cookies to collect personal information. Cookies may also be used by 3rd party content providers such as newsfeeds. 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. 

**Remember The Risks Whenever You Use The Internet**  
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to [Filma24.org](https://www.filma24.org/) and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through Filma24.TV have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies.
